sromobazar.com 2013-04-03

# Sromobazar.Com :: Privacy Policy

This is the Privacy Policy governing your use of the Sromobazar (www.sromobazar.com) site. By using this site, you consent to our Privacy Policy explained below. All terms were not defined in this document that is already mentioned in “Terms of Use Agreement” between you and Sromobazar which you have to accept during the use of this site.

Your privacy is extremely important at Sromobazar. We have developed this policy to ensure that your privacy is well-secured during your use at Sromobazar site.

**We collect the following information:**

**Registration Information**

To be registered user of this site, you will be asked to complete a registration form with your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as your business information (Registration Information).

**Publishing Information**

If you submit any information at Sromobazar to be published through the publishing tools, including but not limited to company Profile, Product Catalog, Trade Leads, Profile and any discussion forum, then you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information ("Publishing Information").

**Payment Information**

If you establish a credit account with us or our providers or if you purchase any product or service from Sromobazar or a vendor available through Sromobazar, we may collect additional information, including billing information, credit card numbers and expiration dates and tracking information from checks s or money orders ("Payment Information").

**Statistical Information**

In addition, we gather aggregate statistical information about our Site and Users, such as IP addresses, browser software, operating system, pages viewed, and number of sessions, unique visitors and so forth ("Statistical Information").

**Collected Information**

The information such as publishing, payment, statistical and any kind of information, which might be collected through the use of cookies or by any other way, can be regarded as “Collected Information”.

**Disclosure of your information**

We do not sell or rent your any personal information to any third party. We disclose information in aggregate for marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose any information that could be used to identify you personally. Some information, such as your password and address, will not be disclosed at all.

In order to maintain a healthy community, Sromobazar would cooperate with all law enforcement inquiries.

We reserve the right to disclose your relevant information as required by law if we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/ or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served.

**Uploading your Contacts**

If a user decides to upload his/her contacts, email invitations will be sent on behalf of the user to everyone on his/her address book. Sromobazar will not store your password. It will only store the name and email address of the contacts for the purpose of sending invitation. It does not sell these email addresses or use these for any kind communication besides invitations and future notifications.

**Your use of other users' information**

You may not use other users' information for commercial purposes, to spam, to harass, or to make unlawful threats. We reserve the right to terminate the accounts of those who misuse other users' information or who otherwise violate the Terms of Use.

**Content Copyright**

Unless otherwise noted, all materials including but not limited to news articles, images, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs that are part of the Sromobazar website (collectively the "Content") are protected by copyright and owned controlled or licensed by Sromobazar.

No Content from the Sromobazar web site may be copied, reproduced, framed, hyperlinked, republished, downloaded, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed by  any way., However,  you may download, where specifically permitted, one copy of the Content on any single computer for your personal, non-commercial use only. Copying or storing of any Content for other than personal use is explicitly prohibited without prior permission from the authority or the copyright holder identified in the copyright notice.

**Inactivity**

You may choose to leave your account dormant for an unlimited period of time.

**Invite a Friend**

If a user decides to use our “Invitation” option to invite a friend to our website, users have an option to add their friend's email addresses. Sromobazar will automatically send an email to invite them to join Sromobazar's website. It stores this email address for the purpose of automatically associating them with the user invitation. It does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations. The friend may contact us to request the removal of this information from our database. By providing information about a friend to us, you can confirm to do so with their consent.

**Minors**

The Site and its contents are not intended to be targeted to minors under applicable law and we do not intend to sell any of our products or services to minors. However, we have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Site and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If a minor has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information.

**Control of your password**

You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If you los control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. This can be done by you, if you click on “Forgot Password” link from user login page and reset your password, you can also change your password from user panel by clicking on “Change Password” Link.

**Security**

Sromobazar has security measures to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Sromobazar uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information by hosting at Sromobazar. Although "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, our technical experts at Sromobazar work hard to ensure your highest level of secured use of our site.

**Security**

Once you register, you will be able to review and change your personal information including: Your  email address, Your Full Name, Your Address, Your Contact No., Your Country Name etc.

Promptly update your information if it changes by signing in to your account and following the screen prompts. We strongly urge you to periodically change your password to help reduce the risk of unauthorized access to your account information.

We welcome any comments or queries you may have. So, please feel free to send a message to our Customer Service Department for the purposes of altering your information or changing your settings.

**Deleting your Profile**

The Administrator of the Sromobazar network has the following right to delete your profile from the Sromobazar database if the user is reported and found to be using unacceptable language or identified as a menace to other users or  displays material online that is offensive to social and religious sensitivities to a region.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posting  as an amended and restated Privacy Policy in  our website The amended and restated Privacy Policy will make  new Privacy Policy effective to the site immediately. You agree that all Collected Information (whether or not collected prior to or after the new policy became effective) will be governed by the newest Privacy Policy then in effect. If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact Sromobazar in writing (at the address set out in the Notice provision of the Terms of Use Agreement) and specifically request that Sromobazar return and/or destroy all copies of all or part of your Collected Information in Sromobazar's possession.

**Cookies**

We use "cookies" to store specific information about you and track your visits to our Site. It is not uncommon for websites to use cookies to enhance identification of their users. A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can be sent to your computer's hard drive only if you access our Site using the computer. If you do not de-activate or erase the cookie, each time you use the same computer to access our Site, our web servers will be notified of your visit to our Site and in turn we may have knowledge of your visit and the pattern of your usage. Generally, we use cookies to identify you and enable us to access your Registration Information, Publishing Information or Payment Information so you do not have to re-enter it; gather statistical information about usage by Users; research visiting patterns and help target advertisements based on User interests; assist our partners to track User visits to the Site and process orders; and track progress and participation in promotions.

You can determine if and how a cookie will be accepted by configuring your browser's which is installed in the computer you are using to access the Site. If you desire, you can change those configurations in your browser. By setting your preferences in the browser, you can accept all cookies, you can be notified when a cookie is sent, or you can reject all cookies. If you reject all cookies by choosing the cookie-disabling function in your browser, you may be required to re-enter your information on our Site more often and certain features of our Site may be unavailable.
